<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>

<swedish>
S: vad kan jag hjälpa dig med
U: jag skulle vilja köpa en hund
S: okej. hur viktigt är det för dig att hunden går att träna på en skala mellan noll till fem
U: två
S: på en skala mellan noll och fem hur viktigt är det för dig att den fäller där noll är att den fäller mycket och fem att den fäller lite
U: fem ehh tre
S: hur viktigt är det för dig att hunden har energi. hur mycket energi ska hunden ha på en skala mellan noll och fem
U: tre
S: och på en skala mellan noll och fem hur mycket skall den skälla
U: två
S: på en skala mellan noll och fem hur beskyddande skall den vara
U: två
S: ja då rekommenderar jag en japanese akita
</swedish>

<english>
A: What can I help you with?
U: I would like to buy a dog
A: okay. how important is it to you that the dog can be trained on a scale between zero and five
U: two
A: on a scale between zero and five how important is it to you that it sheds where zero is that it sheds a lot and five that it sheds a little
U: five uhh three
A: how important is it to you that the dog has energy. how much energy should the dog have on a scale between zero and five
U: three
A: and on a scale between zero and five how much should it bark
U: two
A: on a scale between zero and five, how protective should it be
U: two
A: yes then I recommend a Japanese Akita
</english>

<distillation>
A: What can I help you with?
U: I would like to buy a dog
A: okay. how important is it to you that the dog can be trained on a scale between zero and five
U: two
A: on a scale between zero and five how important is it to you that it sheds where zero is that it sheds a lot and five that it sheds a little
U: five uhh three
A: how important is it to you that the dog has energy. how much energy should the dog have on a scale between zero and five
U: three
A: and on a scale between zero and five how much should it bark
U: two
A: on a scale between zero and five, how protective should it be
U: two
A: yes then I recommend a Japanese Akita
</distillation>

<final>
A: What can I help you with?
U: I would like to buy a dog
A: okay. how important is it to you that the dog can be trained on a scale between zero and five
U: two
A: on a scale between zero and five how important is it to you that it sheds where zero is that it sheds a lot and five that it sheds a little
U: five uhh three
A: how important is it to you that the dog has energy. how much energy should the dog have on a scale between zero and five
U: three
A: and on a scale between zero and five how much should it bark
U: two
A: on a scale between zero and five, how protective should it be
U: two
A: yes then I recommend a Japanese Akita
</final>

</root>