<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>

<swedish>
S: vad kan jag hjälpa dig med
U: jag skulle vilja köpa en hund
S: okej. på en skala mellan noll och fem hur viktigt är det för dig att hunden kan tränas
U: fyra
S: hur mycket skall hunden fälla på en skala mellan noll och fem
U: fyra
S: på en skala mellan noll och fem hur mycket energi skall hunden ha?
U: noll
S: ja. det finns ingen hund som fyller dom 
U: tre då
S: egenskaperna. ja. på en skala mellan noll och fem hur mycket skall hunden skälla
U: skälla
S: skälla ja
U: eh. två
S: okej. då föreslår jag att du skaffar en golden retriever
U: yay
</swedish>

<english>
A: What can I help you with?
U: I would like to buy a dog
A: okay. on a scale between zero and five how important is it to you that the dog can be trained
U: four
A: how much should the dog shed on a scale between zero and five
U: four
S: on a scale between zero and five, how much energy should the dog have?
U: zero
A: yes. there is no dog that fills those
U: three then
A: properties. yes. on a scale between zero and five how much should the dog bark
U: bark
A: bark yes
U: uh. two
A: okay. then I suggest you get a golden retriever
U: yay
</english>

<distillation>
A: What can I help you with?
U: I would like to buy a dog
A: okay. on a scale between zero and five how important is it to you that the dog can be trained
U: four
A: how much should the dog shed on a scale between zero and five
U: four
S: on a scale between zero and five, how much energy should the dog have?
U: zero
A: yes. there is no dog that fills those<insert princip="coherence"> properties</insert>
U: three then
A: <remove princip="coherence">properties. </remove>yes. on a scale between zero and five how much should the dog bark
U: bark
A: bark yes
U: uh. two
A: okay. then I suggest you get a golden retriever
U: yay
</distillation>

<final>
A: What can I help you with?
U: I would like to buy a dog
A: okay. on a scale between zero and five how important is it to you that the dog can be trained
U: four
A: how much should the dog shed on a scale between zero and five
U: four
S: on a scale between zero and five, how much energy should the dog have?
U: zero
A: yes. there is no dog that fills those properties
U: three then
A: yes. on a scale between zero and five how much should the dog bark
U: bark
A: bark yes
U: uh. two
A: okay. then I suggest you get a golden retriever
U: yay
</final>

</root>