<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>


<swedish>
S: vad kan jag hjälpa dig med
U: jag vill köpa en hund
S: okej. kul. då ska jag fråga dig några frågor och så skall vi se om vi kan komma fram till vilken hund som passar dig. så första frågan. i vilken grad skall din hund vara träningsbar
U: i hög grad
S: ja. vilken grad skall din hund fälla
U: låg grad
S: i vilken grad ska din hund ha energi
U: hög grad
S: i vilken grad ska din hund skälla
U: ganska lågt
S: i vilken grad ska din hund vara beskyddande
U: ganska lågt
S: ah. då rekommenderar jag volpino italiano
U: super
</swedish>

<english>
S: What can I help you with?
U: I want to buy a dog
S: okay. nice. then I'll ask you a few questions and then we'll see if we can decide which dog that suits you. so first question. to what degree should your dog be trainable
U: to a great extent
S: yes. to what degree should your dog shed
U: low degree
S: to what degree should your dog have energy
U: high degree
S: to what degree should your dog bark
U: quite low
S: to what degree should your dog be protective
U: quite low
S: ah. then I recommend volpino italiano
U: great
</english>

<distillation>
S: What can I help you with?
U: I want to buy a dog
S: okay. <remove princip="neutrality">nice. </remove>then I'll ask you a few questions and then we'll see if we can decide which dog that suits you. so first question. to what degree should your dog be trainable
U: to a great extent
S: yes. to what degree should your dog shed
U: low degree
S: to what degree should your dog have energy
U: high degree
S: to what degree should your dog bark
U: quite low
S: to what degree should your dog be protective
U: quite low
S: <remove princip="immediacy">ah. </remove>then I recommend <insert princip="syntax">a </insert>volpino italiano
U: great
</distillation>

<final>
S: What can I help you with?
U: I want to buy a dog
S: okay. then I'll ask you a few questions and then we'll see if we can decide which dog that suits you. so first question. to what degree should your dog be trainable
U: to a great extent
S: yes. to what degree should your dog shed
U: low degree
S: to what degree should your dog have energy
U: high degree
S: to what degree should your dog bark
U: quite low
S: to what degree should your dog be protective
U: quite low
S: then I recommend a volpino italiano
U: great
</final>

</root>